<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://nathan7402.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://nathan7402.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2024-09-13T17:17:01+00:00</updated><id>https://nathan7402.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">blank</title><subtitle>A simple, whitespace theme for academics. Based on [*folio](https://github.com/bogoli/-folio) design. </subtitle><entry><title type="html">What is this blog?</title><link href="https://nathan7402.github.io/blog/2024/what-is-this/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What is this blog?"/><published>2024-07-12T20:30:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-07-12T20:30:00+00:00</updated><id>https://nathan7402.github.io/blog/2024/what-is-this</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://nathan7402.github.io/blog/2024/what-is-this/"><![CDATA[<p>I’ve just started this site, and one question begs answering: Why? I’m just some guy, who cares what I do or think? I don’t need a blog.</p> <p>First of all, correct—I don’t need a blog. Here’s why I created one anyway:</p> <ol> <li><strong>This site is an excuse to write.</strong> My current job and lifestyle mean most of the things I create are either long slide decks or short social media posts. Now that I’m no longer in school, I don’t have much reason to write longer-form content. This site gives me an excuse to do so and keep those skills alive.</li> <li><strong>This site is an excuse to learn, think, and reflect.</strong> Writing something down is one of the best ways to organize your thoughts on a topic. I think writing here will help me reflect on my own life and understand myself better. I also hope that it will give me an excuse to nerd out on topics that interest me, and to learn about them in more depth than I would if I wasn’t writing about them as well.</li> <li><strong>This site is a way to document my life.</strong> We all have many, many ways to document our lives now, given the proliferation of social media. But those outlets are often performative, and don’t allow us to capture the complexity of our lives. I’m hoping that on this site I can document my life in a more detailed way, and that someone else finds that valuable as well.</li> <li><strong>This site is mostly for me.</strong> Consider this my public journal. In the short run, it’s not likely that anyone other than me will look at it anyway. This site is a way for me to understand myself and to bring all parts of my identity together.</li> </ol> <p>Truthfully, I don’t know what this site will turn into. I don’t even know if I’ll continue to update it. But for now, as it is born into the world, these are my guiding principles.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="why"/><category term="what"/><category term="basics"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[guiding principles for this site]]></summary></entry></feed>